# **Dawn Ribeiro**

# Full Stack Developer

(863) 446-0726 Email: <a href="mailto:dawnribeiro1006@gmail.com">dawnribeiro1006@gmail.com</a>

GitHub: dawnribeiro LinkedIn: dawn-ribeiro

After nearly two decades as a massage therapist, I was inspired by my husband's career change to explore opportunities as a developer. My history with tailoring customer experience and my history of entrepreneurship have given me the interpersonal skills I need to excel in my new career. Additionally, I have been inspired by my program, my husband, and by the local tech community to explore opportunities as a full-stack developer.

### **SKILLS**

-Customer Service	-JavaScript	-C#	-Slack
-HTML5	-React	Net	-Trello
-CSS3	-SQL	-Git	

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## The Academy at Suncoast Developers Guild, St. Pete, FL - Student

March 2019 - July 2019

12-week intensive program around how to develop full-stack web applications. Starting with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript moving through to SQL and C#, the program culminated in the creation of our own full-stack capstone project.

Color Picker: <a href="https://color-hooks-dawng-ribeiro.netlify.com/">https://color-hooks-dawng-ribeiro.netlify.com/</a>

The color picker is a random color selector for Hue, Saturation and Lightness. This project was built using React.js Hooks

#### Massage Therapy

Massage Envy, Lutz, FL - Massage Therapist

March 2014 - May 2019

Dawn Griffith, LMT, The Studio of Health and Beauty, Sebring, FL- Massage Therapist/Entrepreneur

January 2013 - March 2014

The Studio of Health and Beauty, Sebring, FL -Massage Therapist

January 2006 - January 2013

Developed specific treatment plans for each client

Followed HIPPA and confidentiality laws

#### **EDUCATION**

The Academy at Suncoast Developers Guild, St. Pete, FL - Certificate for Full-Stack Development

March 2019 - July 2019